we are gonna try this out and do it
actually live public not unlisted live
and then i
i then go in and make it public after
it's actually public there might be
people joining so
in case anyone's watching the replay i
just want to introduce myself in case
you came here through the ntmlm
community
because this is not an anti-mlm channel
i am anti-mlm
but this channel is dedicated to my
journey towards
creating a world that works for everyone
and my own personal growth
and learning as it all unfolds
and so part of that journey is that a
few months ago i fell down an anti-mlm
rabbit hole when one of my friends
joined nmlm
and i've always kind of been interested
in the exponential math and so i have
joined a lot of the nt as a subscriber a
lot of the anti-mlm
channels started with key keys i think
the first one i got closely followed by
illuminati
and then it just snowballed from there
so
i seem to join the ntmlm community right
before
all of this drama took place or a couple
months before the drama took place i
don't know when the ntl
mlm community started but it feels like
it's exploding not in a
drama way because everything goes
through drama but in
a so many channels and then people see
that are like oh i could create this
content and creating more and more of it
but i wanted to give um my
take on the anti-mlm drama and community
um just because i want it as part of my
journey
and i do have some opinions on on what
is what is going down
as well as uh but i do
i'm not just anti-mlm i'm
anti-capitalism i'm anti
this entire pyramid ponzi scheme
structure that we're all in right now
and i think part of that
is why i offer a different voice that is
going to be more controversial because
most people
can see why they're anti-mlm but are
pro-capitalistic or like
and i want a business in the bigger
structure i'm not anti-business owner
i'm not anti-working within the system
you have
i'm just a lot of the same critiques we
have about the mlm system can be had
about the capitalist system now falling
down this
anti-mlm rabbit hole i ended up creating
an mlm it's called meta learning magic
which the acronym is mlm
on purpose and it wasn't going to have
the same structure
and it doesn't it is an omni when
everyone wins
structure and yet it honors that the
people in the beginning are taking more
risk
and creating the product and creating
the community and will be able to
hopefully retire
in a with a maximum of 120 000
a year so this no one's gonna become
millionaires out of this
but i did want to like just mention that
i
today's the day we actually launched the
mlm today is the day i launched the
first
the beta of the six week course six
weeks to a better us
i i'm really excited by this and it's
just like the tension i'm currently
playing in
both of um like trying to create
something in a world
that is all about broadcast and all
about and it's where it's going to come
into play in this whole in this whole
live
is um
i'm playing in that tension of like
being anti-capitalistic in a world
that's chemicalistic
in a uh influencer culture in all of the
anti-mlm
content creators and why this drama has
unfolded
so a quick rundown sorry i'm like i'll
forget to log into this and haven't even
gotten to the t
so there is a anti-mlm youtube
personality called kimberlea or she was
anti-youtube when i found her i found
her through the anti-mlm world i didn't
know her from beforehand
and i never jived with her content i i
liked the intellectualism of it like i
liked
i thought she was very smart and well
articulated and so i enjoyed some of the
um individual
shows those are called videos but not
the um not her overall personality
because i found her very capitalistic i
found her very
toxically positive which triggered all
of my stuff about my sister and all my
stuff about capitalism
and so although i can watch something
and be triggered by it and get what i
meant to get out of it
i always found her and it made sense
when she came out as
auntie auntie mlm i don't know she came
out as not being anti-mlm and the way
that she did it
i understand um but it's it's like all
of capitalism
is the reason anyway so sorry so she
came out did a two-hour live
um explaining why she wasn't auntie emma
anymore
and basically it was because the
anti-ammo community is
is bullies and toxic and whatever she
goes on for two hours
which then she was critiqued because it
was two hours like it was a live you
don't necessarily edit lives that's why
i do lives because i don't edit video
there's also why i'm not an ntmlm
youtube creator
is i don't edit so i'm not really a
youtube creator i'm doing this
this this channel all of it for me and
my journey and like my future fans if
that makes any sense if i have future
fans once i've saved the world if
people happen to know me i seem to be
designing the way to save the world
without me being known for it
which is great because that is my little
introvert self would love that
but i also have to be open to the fact
that i might be known and so
if there needs to be a let's see where
this came from my brain won't be able to
tell you i won't be able to tell you 10
years from now
what this 10-year journey looked like
and so i'm trying to showcase it some of
it's unlisted some of it's private and
some of it is absolutely public
and i try to do as much public as
possible the more it's like you're
getting less professionalism as i go on
less thumbnails because now
i've managed i joined social media
thinking because it was the only way to
get
influence in order to get people in
order to create a world that worked for
everyone
and now i see that it is the exact
opposite of how i will be doing it
but um anyway so kimberly i did two hour
a video
basically crapping on the ntlm community
but also speaking her truth that she
basically was here for the
for the views here because the algorithm
helped her grow
and she's not passionate about it
anymore and the very thing she wants to
do
doesn't want to do which is reaction
videos of her watching content of people
in mlms same things and their training
videos and then reacting to them which
is where oh it is the stuff we end up
watching
but then all because there's so many of
these creators out there we end up we
end up watching
the same clip in an mlm
be commented on by multiple people which
does get boring
and old and so the anti-mlm community
is saturated we're about like that is
actually what's happening
we've created our own little mlm where
it's like you can be successful too no
no you can't be there aren't enough
viewers there aren't enough people care
about anti-mlm content
for everybody to have a hundred thousand
viewers because we can't watch all of
your content it just isn't
and so anyway so kimberly i did a
two-hour live video like i said she's
not my personality i don't like her but
she also
copyright straw striked um
and starts with the t either she's not
one of the people i only just kind of
found her through the ante malem drama
um and it would copyright wrote strike
her
i have my favorite anti-mlm people a
handful of people of whom
i found kiki's channel and i love kiki i
can't remember what her actual name is i
tried to remember before this video and
i was like whatever she calls herself
kiki
on if that's what her tag is known as
that's what i'm gonna call her
um that i love her personality
but i'm not there for anything but the
anti-mlm stuff um
or the scam stuff so so that's the other
thing is the anti-mlm people came
through and to anti-alim generally for
being in an mlm the ones that are true
and real
and so they generally have a niche that
goes alongside the anti-mlm
so like deanna got involved in beachbody
and
she also has a vibe of like be caring
about nutrition and caring about that
type of stuff strangely enough
um there's people who come to it through
more of like the monet side and more of
the beauty side and i think
like kiki i don't think ever joined mlm
but that side of it then they end up
going on to creating like
um makeup tutorials or shopping
tutorials just like kiki does not
tutorials
how to shop but like unboxings and stuff
we do not need a how to shop
capitalism nobody doesn't need that and
i'm not i don't really like the
unboxings they're not my thing because
i'm anti-capitalistic
and yet i love her um deanna i like love
her personality
she's just a sweetheart and i really i
really enjoy
my husband caller monica that's not her
name margaret
and gel i think how she says her name
i'm really bad at pronouncing things
but she says it constantly enough that i
think i have that right
um i love her personality and i'll even
watch her put on makeup
because that's how much i like her her
personality comes through
i really like madison from i can't
remember her channel happy's
mine something about happy minds cro
girl world happy mind is i think
yay brain um and
everyone has their own personality but i
did from emily leah who also so emily
lee also did
a a video saying she's not auntie mlm
and her
seemed to ring very true it seemed to
i enjoyed her content well enough but it
seemed very
off the assembly line like yeah making
the same thing churning it out for the
algorithm
unlike deanna who makes a lot of content
and i don't watch all of diana's content
but i don't find she's churning it out
in the same way
like it's it's i can feel her passion in
it whereas emily leah i never found her
passionate about it and i didn't know
why i just thought it was just her
personality
and then when she was like i'm not
anti-mlm anymore it became very clear
she was only here for the algorithm
and in the video where she states she
goes
she's like she smiles just talking about
her business pod that she's gonna do
and she smiled and she's like i've never
smiled in one of these
and yeah do what you love and this is my
big problem with the whole auntie lem
thing
um it brings up a lot of i'm just trying
to stay on topic
so that's what happened 10 minutes in
that's the tea you can go get that tia
much better than any other
any other of the anti-mlm ones if that's
what you're concerned about but i'm here
about
my journey what i'm here to learn and
what i got when i was just watching
madison's
takedown of it was um
oh the difference between what not
necessarily any individuals are doing
but just drama and in general
is that if you're looking for the drama
or even if you're looking to not
perpetuate the drama there's a very big
difference of
that person is wrong or the community is
wrong versus
none of that matters i'm here to learn
from me right i watched kimberlea
because i knew she would trigger me and
i would learn things from being
triggered cool what am i here for what
am i here for like when she talks about
the like purity of the influencers
against the mlm i'm like you guys are
all in the same boat to me
and but yet there were ones that i
connected with where i'm like
i like your personality i don't think
you're just here for the money and the
algorithm
so they're the ones who you and i ended
up anyway
um fighting with more but
this thing i talk about constantly in
the project that i'm doing of profit
versus purpose
and how you can only serve one of those
is your master are you here for the
purpose
are you here for profit and the anti-mlm
community
couldn't be more versed in that people
who i think are here for the purpose
even though they're also getting profit
off of it um i do feel like illuminati's
here for because of just what she covers
on the rest of her
her her stuff um she chooses to cover
other scams some of which i agree with
some which i don't we're we're
we're different on one of her big topics
um that isn't to do with business
but she but i enjoy hers i feel like she
is here for that but she also has not
like
she also it's hard to make decisions
purely for purpose
where your profit is also there but it's
like which one's your master you're here
to create content for you that you enjoy
creating
because then it makes sense and that's
part of what kimberley was saying was
like
she doesn't enjoy the content that gets
gets her the most views
and so should she continue making it no
but of course her personality is going
to tell her she should
because her she's here for profit she i
don't think she was ever unclear about
that
she was like i found the algorithm the
algorithm worked
and you could tell by the way she shows
up that's what she was doing
um and emily leah a little bit of the
same thing
and she came to that realization i think
while watching kimberlea do her so i
think she looked
to kimberlea as somewhat of a auntie mlm
and youtuber idol
and was like oh yeah i'm in the same
boat as her
but hers actually seemed more genuine
like oh
like she didn't even realize that's what
she was doing until she realized it and
then wanted to get out of it and a lot
of the same critiques she had about mlm
people
she was being put back on her and she
was like yeah which is
personal growth which is like oh what
i'm doing to you what i'm critical of
you doing to others is what i'm doing to
you
and i see that in every community all
the time
and this is part of the issue is when
you look at a community
as an individual she's always going to
piss you off
like if you look at any group of people
oh there's a whole person watching
i'm not used to doing these live at the
moment i don't know if you're a game b
person or an anti-mlm person um anyway
that there's a
if you're a gambie person you might not
want to watch this
that there is a um
what's it getting into that piece of if
you're here for purpose or profit
um if you're here for profit then you're
going to create your entire content to
get you the most money
and therefore you're going to your soul
is going to leave from it and people
aren't going to be there for the purpose
that you were there for anyway
um but you can still somewhat do that in
a market that isn't saturated
but the ant alone community is saturated
there's enough anti-mlm content creators
we do not need any more but the
individual might need to put it out
there
right that's different but
if there are people who are here for the
purpose of trying to get people to not
be
oh yeah hello i know who you are i won't
say your name about this one but yeah
um welcome welcome
uh that there is this purpose versus
profit that i can see in the world in
game b
in how we're creating game b that we're
hopefully focusing more on purpose
more on yes we don't need to have the um
any industry the transportation industry
the food industry the
healthcare industry they're all there to
make profit and so that's their first
priority and they'll kind of deal with
their purpose they'll get you there
fast enough in transportation so that
you don't leave they'll get you food
enough calories you live
but they're not there to nourish you
they're not there to make you healthy
they're not there to actually transport
you
whereas if we concentrate on the purpose
that is
then we're like right transportation but
we have to be profitable enough to stay
in business
that flips everything on its head and in
the anti-mlm world
that all of these people these content
creators are either there for their
purpose
to be in the world to create content to
um to
inform people about the mlm and why it's
a toxic structure
or they're there for profit and i don't
think you can be an influencer
and remain there for purpose it is it
takes a whole other level of an
individual to be like okay i would
rather
do this unboxing but my client my
clients
my audience would rather me do a um
reaction video so you're going to pick
the reaction video because your money's
dependent
on it and you're more subscribers like
even the way that they talk about
subscribers right we are collective
group they don't care that this one
individual subscribed to them they care
about the masses of individuals that
subscribe to them
like the person who just commented on my
video if you're still the one watching
i know this person i've had
conversations with this person
i like this person we have enjoyable
conversations
he is not just a subscriber to me i
don't care about the number i care about
the
the connection and the um relationship
with individual people and in fact when
i
when it's a mass of people even people
i'm having an actual conversation with
online
unless i've met you in in real life
video chat to me is real life
i um you're not a real person
so i don't think of you like it's you're
part of an amalgamist group as opposed
to an individual that's just me other
people i know can distinguish between
those
online but there's a very big difference
of creating for myself
and creating for the world that i want
to create that i want to live into
versus creating things for the youtube
algorithm
it's funny because one of my comments
what was my comment this morning
something about the
oh someone we're talking about
cooperatives and such and someone was
like how do you decide
oh i got introduced to somebody who
wasn't it was like socialist but not
marxist who everyone else probably knows
and the name
written is different than how it's
pronounced so i'm not gonna remember the
name but it's about mutualism and such
and someone's like well how do you
decide it's based on hourly work and i
have an issue with us getting paid based
on hourly work because of my disability
i only have
way less hours than most people but
innovation wise i
have a lot of innovative ideas and so if
we're only paying on labor i have a
problem with that and for only pain on
innovative ideas i have a problem with
that especially since
all of these thought thinkers to do with
labor
were like from the 1800s early 1900s we
didn't have automation we didn't have
like labor's going away
innovation isn't anyway so um i asked i
was like so what
if you did this video and someone else
you took 100 hours through this video
and someone else took 10 hours to do
this video
but it's the same basically the same
content same informative same
entertaining
around the same length you get paid do
you get paid more based because you
spent more time
or do you get paid equal because the
audience gets the same amount of time
out of it or
that i was like do you get paid based on
the amount of people who watch and how
happy they are with it
oh my god youtube has already done you
like you've already done mutualism
that's like that's kind of what they're
doing
or they figured out their own thing like
that did almost seem the most fair
and yet the algorithm breaks everything
else in
our our gaming world and so influencer
culture
the issue is gossip and drama cells
so we click on the titles that are
dishing the t on the anti-mlm community
or like i
when one content creator you know was
part of it has something to say about
the other content creator and they
create titles so we want to click on it
and then therefore they're more likely
to create more drama and have more of
those things going on
because they get more views and it's a
perpetuated system
in in our social media which i know cnn
goggles you are
you're on you're dealing with it our our
attention
is decided by like our basest emotions
which is okay if you're aware of that i
know mine are still decided on my basis
emotions but when i feel triggered by
someone else there's my learning there
and so in watching all of this anti-mlm
content
there's part of me that is
i knew like i was having this
conversation with one of the um
bigger up mlm people in monet on
instagram
and i both wasn't so down with her
because she seems like a very kind
person and her people were attacking me
but she was in my dms being like oh i'm
sorry my people are attacking me i was
like wait a minute why are you
commenting on their actual comments but
i was like i'm a big girl i can take
care of myself you're just mental
capitalism if i can't handle some mlm
hands coming at me
i got a problem but i did realize i was
putting this person
as like the representative for mlms or
this mlm in particular
as opposed to dealing with what she was
actually saying and doing and that is a
lot of what
like i see a lot of the anti alum stuff
as baleen we're
we're picking apart what somebody looks
like or that they're using their
their pieces of their life and it's like
yeah because they believe in it that's a
very big difference using
if you believe in the mlm you're part of
and you're using your miscarriage or
you're using the birth of your child or
you're using the death of a loved one to
sell that
yeah because it's part of your story and
part of who you are and part of like
there's a lot that comes in where it's
like okay are we critiquing mlm
and the predatory structure or
critiquing the person
and i don't want to critique the person
i don't want to belittle people on what
they look like or they were stupid for
getting involved in it
because i've been involved in mlms and
most people in the auntie animal
community have been involved with one
and so like how could you like the
person who got me involved in the auntie
ellen community though i am still like
oh my god how
how how did you do that based on who she
is sorry i'm just gonna
pop this up here so i can actually read
it marketing is so important it might be
good to have gossipy stuff going on
because attention is still attention
even if it's gossip yeah exactly exactly
that is exactly what happens and then we
they create more of it and then they're
like how dare you create it and they're
in a very saturated niche
and so although yes they're all bud like
they're they are literally recreating
the mlm drama of like the community
uh that isn't really a community once
once you start poking holes in it
the product that is like yes but they're
slinging the product too and they
represent
the same one it's anti-mlm and it's like
if we can deal with people as
individuals there isn't an
anti-mlm community we didn't get
together and vote on and decide
like yes this is what we represent
it's just that we don't like mlms and we
see them
as um predatory and yet in that world me
dealing with my
in the anti-mlm community right being
triggered by content creators and having
my solution raisings and doing all of
that
my little brain developed an mlm that's
gonna save the world and so
like the irony in that is because i
wasn't focused on the drama i wasn't
focused on
oh my god did you see what they did i
mean i was a little bit don't get me
wrong that's part of it is being in that
that and being like oh i feel like i'm
in junior high that's interesting
that's really interesting which is also
i don't know why i need to mention this
but
um madison was talking about how
kimberley should know better because
she's like almost 40
and and uh emilia is only like 18 19.
i was like i feel called out here
because i'm 40 i feel like i'm like 18
19. my body feels like it's 80.
my soul feels like i don't even know
simultaneously it's it's 7
and infinity it's all it's
all tied together
like how and so i am i did actually put
out to one of the anti-mlm groups that
i'm part of on facebook to do a solution
raising on mlms which we'll be doing
a week from this thursday if people take
me up on it i had someone request one
that wasn't during the workday i was
like
okay me and my brain will figure it out
for one day to be there
at i think i said 5 p.m so we'll see how
my brain
does we'll see we'll see how it works at
5pm and today in a few hours we're doing
the very
first day of meta learning magic
which is my mlm the mlm i'm creating
that
where it's completely different than all
of the other ones that are out there
which is why i can be anti-mlm and
create an mlm
is because i'm here first and foremost
to dismantle capitalism
and create a world that works for
everyone and without using that exact
language because
you can't really create something by
dismantling something you have to create
something
not just like destroying something still
important especially if it's destructive
but it's not the same as creating
something and so i just asked one of the
other groups that i'm part of it's
getting triggered all over the place i
love it
um about creating a moneyless society
and they're trying to create a
cooperative and you if anyone knows me
i'm all about cooperatives that's how i
got onto youtube it's like we're going
to have a global cooperative
and when i say cooperative i mean very
much consumer cooperative
which i hate the word consumer so it's a
user cooperative but there's i know
cooperatives
and then people are like just coming to
cooperative ideas just
my family just coming to understand what
mondragon is like have you ever heard of
mondragon
yeah decades ago when i first started
talking or a decade ago when i first
started talking about it
and there's that that like weird tension
we're having in the world right now of
like both
why won't the world wake up to what i
know and simultaneously
as they wake up how are you just waking
up to this and like we can't help it
both ways
it's like it does frustrate me anyway
that these people in the in
are like we're going to start a
cooperative and like right what
cooperative one that dismantles
capitalism is basically what they're
saying
and i'm like you can't that can't be the
purpose of that can't be the mission of
your cooperative it has to be
pro-something not anti-something
it has to be and weirdly talking about
the nt11 community
but in this case it is it's about the
mlm community not being there
because it's toxic and because it's
predatory towards people and so yes that
is actually what they're doing you will
know we have succeeded in anti-mlm when
mlms aren't allowed
ironically i might make that more
feasible
by creating my mlm because my mlm is
here to create a world that works for
everyone and so
the powers that be might decide to then
like
mlms are not allowed none of this
structure is allowed even though they
would have
a really hard time ever doing that to us
not them
because ours has none of the predatory
structure that they would have to cancel
us over without canceling them but they
might they might find a way for sure
um when i get to any of this gossip
sells drama cells
money is what a lot of these people
especially kimberlea i wouldn't say
emily leah i don't think she was
necessarily seeking money but i do think
she found a niche and was like oh i'm
getting subscribers but she built her
entire thing on this so that now to
change and become auntie mlm
it's going to hurt her algorithm and she
actually learned a lot on how to edit
video and how to do thumbnails i'm sure
and how to build an audience and engage
with an audience
and if she was doing that on content she
wasn't passionate about doing it on
business doing on something she was
passionate about i think will be
will be good uh mlms oh that's what i
have here just that mlms are
they are capitalism like they're
microcosm capitalism so if you can
critique
an mlm but you can't critique capitalism
um i think it's a lot of of seeing what
you don't like in yourself in the world
and then yelling at it
because i don't know what is it that's
in an mlm that isn't in capitalism
because i'm anti-capitalism so maybe i
can't see it
but then i also through being anti-mlm
created an mlm that's going to destroy
capitalism so
it's it's all kinds of ironic and
chaotic which welcome to me
mlms are toxic they're top-heavy this is
what i mean when i say mlms or like
capitalism
capitalism itself is very top-heavy it's
designed to be a pyramid it's designed
to have very few people at the top and
to make you feel bad if you're at the
bottom if you're at the bottom it's
because you're lazy and you're not
working hard enough and it's on you
the people at the top got to the top
just fine what's wrong with you and yes
and mlm's literally designed that you
can't do that once you get in near the
bottom but so is
capitalism good luck creating the next
amazon the next facebook is already here
yes you might call it the new innovative
idea
but that's one out of billions of people
right that's that's
millionaires are made in the mlm
community in fact more millionaires are
made in the mlm community than most
other
industries just because of how they are
designed we're going to recreate that
but not get anyone to millionaire
status get people to 120 000 a year
status
it's not status access to resources uh
so the other thing besides the top-heavy
business structure which
very capitalistic is this personality of
toxic conformity of like
okay if you're oh my god even in
the moneyless society rbe space
i think it was that one someone's
talking about a co-op and someone was
like i think we should create a plastics
co-op like it's the only option the
other person's like that's not very
professional this way you're dealing
with it i'm like if you think you're
only going to deal with professional
people
like this is we have neurodiversity
coming up all over the place and we need
it
our current society requires people to
be very professional and look a very
specific way for us to trust them
with our money or with our sense-making
capacity
they're not necessarily the people we
should be trusting in fact the world
should be flipped on its head the very
people
who are like i was just watching a
little bit of matilda with my kid
and that the i remember her name is um
this is
the bad guy in it looks horrible right
she's got like moles on her face and her
teeth are gross
and that is what we grew up thinking a
bad guy was right disney villains it's
like they're just like
hunched over and they look grotesque and
they
good luck being now those people are if
they exist in the real world we're
probably made a bad guy because
the how the world treats them because
how they look they're they weren't evil
people that became
ugly on the outside they were ugly and
some of those ugly people became ugly on
the inside because of how we treated
them
but more and more beautiful people are
ugly
beautiful people who think that the
world
they deserve what the world gives them
the world's super kind to me i don't
know what your problem is yeah because
you're gorgeous that's not the same for
everybody else
and so our very like what we should be
when we see someone we see they're
pretty
our genetic self are like
we're looking to breed with them or
something and we think they're a better
person yeah they might be a better
person to breed with except even that's
a lie because they probably had cosmetic
surgery they're definitely wearing
makeup they probably have photoshop
their shirt if you're just looking at a
photo
but the but they also grew up in a world
where they had very little draw very
little
stuff to overcome very little and so
really
the more beautiful you are the probably
the less likely you are to be a good
person the less likely you are to be
able to be a competent leader
and yet we're going to give you the role
and we do that time and time again in
society the people that can sound
intelligent
even though they don't know the f
they're talking about are
going to be who we give the roles right
we give the roles to the over estimators
not the underestimators and we should be
dealing with the underestimators if you
look at autism itself
i would prefer our politicians and ceos
to all be autistic
hands down but we're never gonna put
them in power so now the odd one can get
in because they can mask and
we're damn good at masking so the ones
that are good at masking can be even
better at that but that's basically why
politicians and then we're there is
because they're really good at lying and
putting on a persona
so that's who we have in the positions
of power and so this personality
conformity cult
happens in capitalism in our democracies
just the same as it does in lms
we just it's slightly bigger right like
like a cult is a very small
is a much smaller box and mlms are just
capitalistic cults um capitalism in
general our society in general has a
slightly bigger box you're accepted in
but it's still a box you're still not
allowed to be on the outside you're
still not allowed to be
and so it's it's can we design the box
to be bigger
can you be a can you just have any
personality and be part of a system
i think that would be the best for the
individual in the system
and then uh the other part is this this
idea of products in general
that in an mlm there's this like idea
that the products there to help you and
if
it was illegal it wouldn't be there if
it was toxic it wouldn't be there it's
like the fda simultaneously will save
you and is the devil
it's like they didn't okay it but they'd
also come in and stop it if it was too
bad no
they didn't no it doesn't work that way
and that's the same with
basically a lot of the products on our
shelves now are they making people
die like just keel over and die no but
they're causing cancer and infertility
and all these things in the long run
and yet we we're like well they're on
the shelf so they have to be safe
or well the company it's like no company
is there for you they're there to make
profit mlms are just another layer of
like they don't have the liability
because they can
hire people they don't actually hire to
market and sell their product to their
connections
and they can lie about it and they're
the ones that are liable instead of them
but they're the
lies are coming from down telephone all
the way down
and so those are the three like
it's taught it's a top-heavy structure
the personality cult stills exists and
the products are still crap and we only
trust them because of marketing
whereas all of those things we could do
better right we can create products that
we trust because we know what's in them
and it's transparent
and if it we can choose what
preservatives are in it and is it the
trade-off worth it right like we can
create things that
even if we're not involved the people
that are involved we can trust because
they're not there for profit
they're there for purpose as soon as you
make profit the driving factor if you
get people to create a company
that creates goods and profits their
driving factor
then they're going to lie about what's
in it and they're going to try and scam
other people
they're going to try to like well they
lied so i've got to lie a little bit
more and a little bit more and we
recreate what we have
if we can have transparency and truth we
can create products that we act and
services that we actually trust
the personality that like it's
uncomfortable to be with people who
don't act the way you thought that they
should and they're not doing it that way
and it's like yep
welcome to humanity that is if if
somebody's triggering you
you can you can yell at them to change
spoiler alert they're probably not going
to or you can change and realize that
you're probably reacting to your
reaction to them
rather than what they're actually they
said something you think they said
something else you think that their tone
is different so i don't type online
this is conversation this plastic i had
a great idea for cooperative and the
cooperative people were like we're just
going to create an anti-capitalistic
cooperative
i can't work with you you're not you're
not professional i was like i'd rather
work with the other guy any day
because he doesn't require
professionalism and actually his idea is
really great
and i can see i can i can feel it in my
body because i feel it that frustration
when people come to mondragon now
instead of a decade ago when i was like
i've been talking about this for a
decade
i've i've surpassed it i know think
worker cooperatives are the solution
because they were only the solution if
they started decades ago
right but people have to catch up to
that before they can surpass it
but i get frustrated because i'm like no
consumer cooperative what's wrong with
you
but it's like that tension it's hard to
not let anger or frustration come out
when you're typing or when you're
talking
and sometimes being autistic i look
frustrated or angry but i'm not
like i don't know why that sounds
it just does funny
doesn't feel but it sounds
coming out of my mouth
that there's yeah personality we can we
can create a
a culture of inclusivity of authenticity
and that is what we are going to do in
better learning magic and it's going to
be messy
but luckily i just figured out a week i
don't need to create a culture that
works for 7.5 billion people
i have to create a culture that works
for me literally
i've invited five other people to be
part of this conversation today
and they're all people that i love that
i feel comfortable with i can show up
and make a mess
no problem they're used to it they've
shown up to my other stuff and i've made
a mess
and i'm gonna invite them to make messes
and they can invite people we can invite
people that we feel comfortable enough
so hopefully if they don't work in our
time slot they work in their time slot
but like we're growing something that's
like do we feel comfortable showing up
as ourselves
how do we invite other people to feel
comfortable showing up as themselves and
how do we actually create that culture
if we fail at it none of us are getting
220 thousand dollars a year
and if we succeed at it million a
million of us are getting to
retire to a cooperative system not at
120 000
but and we can create
a non-top heavy i mean that's literally
what our mlm is doing meta learning
magic
is creating something that isn't top
heavy i'll be the first person because
i'm the founding member i'm the one
looking for the 10 who will find the 100
will find the thousand
that we i'm the first person to make it
to 120 000.
the next round the 10 people below me
join me and the next round 100 people
below them join them and the next round
1 000 people below them join them
and so it's not and then i'm making a
million
120 is the cap so you can't make more
than that so you're going to need to
make your standard of living better with
ingenuity and innovation
not through just making more money and
we
anyway i love that this ann taylorman
thing anti-mlm thing is blowing up i
think it is because we're looking at it
like
it's individuals like if we do this all
the time with any group
right why in the world do women both
want me to pull the chair out for them
and yell at me when i pull the chair out
for them
because they're different women simple
as that
one loves it one doesn't one thinks
you're like stepping on her feminism one
feels cared for
they're not the same people women didn't
get together and decide should we have
the chair pulled
out for us or not right that's not same
thing i can probably find one for men
too right
men want to pay for the check men get
offended if i expect them to pay for the
check it's like
yeah different men it's like it's
different and so dealing with people as
different
and realizing everywhere we want a
blanket statement people and realizing
am i dealing with people as an
individual
or as a group and am i dealing with what
was actually said and i can actually
like or am i dealing with what i what i
made what they said mean am i dealing
with what actually happened or am i
dealing with what
um happened and what i meant mean about
it because 99
of the time we are reacting to our
interpretation of what they said our
story around what they said
and so anyway yeah anti-capital and i
am anti-mlm and in falling down that
rabbit hole i'm creating the mlm that is
going to create
create a world that works for everyone
and i get to do it without
without the word becoming an influencer
because god knows i wasn't gonna become
an influencer with my 250 subscribers
and it's never getting like
i want
10 000 people not following me following
themselves
following their own inner guidance who
are willing to put in 25 a month so we
have a pool of resources to create
all of the systems and all of the tools
we need that constantly come out of
solution raisings and come out of
conversations
and are the same tech created time and
time and time again but the reason it
didn't work because it didn't have the
threshold of users
didn't have enough resources to get it
wasn't quite it wasn't quite the right
tool
we together can take on the risk
together we can create something so
powerful and so amazing and that's why
i'm on here despite the fact not wanting
to be an influencer
not wanting to have broadcast culture
because i don't want to ever choose
my choose profit over purpose and i
think i'm pretty safe in that
i think that i'm pretty safe in who i am
as an individual i will choose people
over purpose
i won't choose profit over purpose you
pay me for something it
loses value it doesn't start gaining
value but in living in that world i've
created a way that will retire
millions of us to create cooperative and
unlike the mlms that are just like any
warm body in the seat
this isn't any warm body in the sea this
is like the first
one ten hundred thousand ten thousand
need to be people who are
cooperative who want a cooperative
system who want to help themselves and
help
everybody else and can deal with their
own that comes up as they go
and so that's not just everyone in fact
it's going to turn off the very people
it should turn off
and bring in the very people it should
bring in it's like well you're not
we're not handing you 120 000 are you
going to build this with us
no buy yes let's see
what level do you want to be on do you
want to be on this level it comes with
more responsibility
pays out sooner this level less
responsibility pays out later
you can choose where you're in but they
come with different responsibility which
one do you want to be at
and so right now i'm i'm having a six
week course
and we're looking at it's called six
weeks to a better us and we're it's
all we hopefully always going to be
there and improving constantly and
always be free
so anyone can come and participate in a
six-week course
get coach crowd coaching where we're
able to help each other
solve our problems you don't need an
expert you don't need anyone with more
information than you have you're the
expert in your own life
how can we improve our lives together
and on the sixth week of that
six week course i'm going to introduce
people to meta learning magic
like do you want to come build this
thing and then people can say yes or no
and decide which
level they're at
i'm excited today's the day it starts
and cnn goggles is i'm not saying you're
it is goggles in our googles google
spawns uh
dmv if you're if you're interested our
six week course is full
but we're this is the beta we're going
to be doing more and more and more and
you're of course are invited
anyone else i know by actual name or if
this just really excites for wants to
get to actually know me on video chat
not one way video chat is uh more than
invited to come and now i've gotta oh go
get my kid on on i was on for way longer
than i thought it was gonna be
i gotta go bye